<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>

<addon id="repository.coreelec-il" name="coreELEC-IL Repository" version="1.0.1"
    provider-name="kicking-bird-py | CoreELEC-IL">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="coreELEC-IL Repository">
    <dir>
    <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kicking-bird-py/coreelec-il/main/addons.xml</info>
    <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kicking-bird-py/coreelec-il/main/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
    <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kicking-bird-py/coreelec-il/main/zips</datadir>
    </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">The Official coreELEC-IL Community Repository</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Install addons from coreELEC-IL</description>
        <summary lang="he_IL">המאגר הרשמי של קהילת coreELEC-IL</summary>
        <description lang="he_IL">התקנת הרחבות מבית coreELEC-IL</description>
        
        <news>
            [v1.0.1] - coreELEC-IL Repository Update
            - Added Safe Boot Manager addon (service.safeboot.manager).
            - Added support for service providers: Trakt, TorBox, AllDebrid, Real-Debrid, Premiumize and EasyNews.
            - On first install, select which providers to enable — checked on every boot.
            - If not connected, a prompt appears to connect directly without digging through POV settings.

            [v1.0.0] - coreELEC-IL Repository Launch
            - Added new addon to Program category: AutoCompletion [CoreELEC-IL Edition].
            - Server configuration and folder structure update.
        </news>


        
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This addon is provided AS-IS. Developed and verified for the CoreELEC-IL community on Homatics hardware running the NG version. Use on other systems at your own risk.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he_IL">התוסף מסופק כפי שהוא (AS-IS). פותח ואומת עבור קהילת CoreELEC-IL על גבי חומרת Homatics בגרסת NG. שימוש על מערכות אחרות הוא על אחריות המשתמש.</disclaimer>

        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
    
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.autocompletion"
       name="AutoCompletion [CoreELEC-IL Edition]" 
       version="3.0.1"
       provider-name="Philipp Temminghoff, sualfred, xulek, kicking-bird-py | CoreELEC-IL">
    
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.1" />
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="plugin.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Optimized Autocompletion Engine for POV [CoreELEC-IL]</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">High-performance version featuring Hebrew RTL fixes, smart caching, and exclusive POV search optimization. 
                                Verified on Homatics Box R 4K Plus running CoreELEC NG.
                                *** NOTE: This addon requires a supported skin. Examples: Arctic Fuse, Arctic Horizon 2 (AH2), Titan BINGE, FENtastic, Nimbus, and Embuary. ***</description>

        <summary lang="he_IL">מנוע השלמה אוטומטית משופר ל-POV [CoreELEC-IL]</summary>
        <description lang="he_IL">גרסה מיועלת ומהירה הכוללת תיקוני עברית (RTL), מערכת Caching חכמה ואופטימיזציית POV. 
                                    נבדק ואומת על Homatics Box R 4K Plus תחת CoreELEC גרסת NG.
                                *** שים לב: תוסף זה מחייב סקין תומך המטמיע את המנגנון במקלדת. סקינים תומכים לדוגמה: Arctic Fuse, Arctic Horizon 2 (AH2), Titan BINGE, FENtastic, Nimbus, ו-Embuary. ***</description>
                                
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This addon is provided AS-IS. Developed and verified for the CoreELEC-IL community on Homatics hardware running the NG version. Use on other systems at your own risk.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he_IL">התוסף מסופק כפי שהוא (AS-IS). פותח ואומת עבור קהילת CoreELEC-IL על גבי חומרת Homatics בגרסת NG. שימוש על מערכות אחרות הוא על אחריות המשתמש.</disclaimer>

        <news lang="en_GB">
                [v3.0.1] - Bug Fix Update
                - [Fix] 'clean_for_provider' is now actually invoked before sending text to POV (it was defined but never called in v3.0.0).
                - [Fix] The cleaning logic now also strips trailing season/episode/part numbers attached to garbage words (e.g. "Season 8", "עונה 8"), not just the word itself.
                - [Improvement] Rebuilt the cleaning dictionary into categorized, prefix-aware rules (Hebrew prefixes like ה-/ו-/ש- are now recognized) with full English-language support added alongside Hebrew.

                [v3.0.0] - CoreELEC-IL Major Update
                - [Architecture] Integrated Package: Script and modules are built-in. No additional addons or dependencies will be installed.
                - [UX] Ready-to-Use: No manual settings required. Search language and RTL are pre-configured for Hebrew.
                - [Requirement] REQUIRES a supported skin: Arctic Fuse, AH2, Titan BINGE, FENtastic, Nimbus, Embuary, etc.
                - [Hardware] Fully verified on Homatics Box R 4K Plus (CoreELEC NG version).
                - [Development] Full Python 3 migration and code rewrite.
                - [POV Optimization] Implemented 'clean_for_provider' logic to maximize search hits.
                - [Performance] Added 7-day intelligent caching and 10s network timeout.
        </news>


        <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
        <website>https://github.com/kicking-bird-py/open-source/plugin.program.autocompletion</website>
        <source>https://github.com/kicking-bird-py/open-source/plugin.program.autocompletion</source>
    </extension>
</addon>  
    <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.safeboot.manager"
       name="Safe Boot Manager"
       version="1.0.5"
       provider-name="kicking-bird-py | CoreELEC-IL">

    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login"/>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <source>https://github.com/kicking-bird-py/coreelec-il</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>

        <summary lang="en_gb">Saving Kodi from crashing every time you click your remote like crazy.</summary>
        <summary lang="he_il">התוסף שיציל את המערכת מקריסה בכל פעם שאתם לוחצים על השלט כמו משוגעים.</summary>

        <description lang="en_gb">
            We all know the drill: Kodi boots up, you rush to press the remote, and BAM – everything freezes and goes to sleep. Especially on (Kodi – CoreELEC) systems or those slow-morning streamers.
            Instead of pulling the power plug, this add-on is here to save your sanity:
            * Startup Guardian: Safely blocks your trigger-happy fingers for a few seconds during boot, while showing a nice status bar until it's safe to click.
            * Exit &amp; Transition Protection: Cleans up memory behind the scenes so your streamer won't have a mini heart attack when you exit a movie too fast.
            * The Panic Button: Video acting up? Don't hunt for the stop button. Just press the Back key 3 quick times, and it will force-close the player instantly.
            Everything can be easily changed or turned off in the settings, so you can click in peace.
        </description>

        <description lang="he_il">
            כולנו מכירים את זה: המכשיר נדלק, אתם ממהרים ללחוץ על השלט כדי לראות משהו, ובום – הכל קופא ונתקע. זה קורה המון במערכות (Kodi – CoreELEC), או בסטרימרים שמתעוררים לאט בבוקר.
            במקום לנתק מהחשמל, התוסף הזה בא לעשות סדר בבלאגן:
            * בועת הגנה בהדלקה: חוסמת לכם את האצבע לכמה שניות כשהמערכת עולה, ומראה לכם בסטייל שהכל נטען בשקט ברקע. בלי פאניקה.
            * הגנה ביציאה ובמעברים: מנקה את הזיכרון מאחורי הקלעים כדי שהסטרימר לא יחטוף התקף לב כשאתם יוצאים מהר מדי מסרט או מחליפים ערוצים.
            * כפתור מילוט מהיר: נתקע הנגן? אל תחפשו את כפתור העצירה. 3 לחיצות מהירות על כפתור החזור בשלט – והסרט נסגר בשבילך בצורה בטוחה.
            אפשר לשנות, לכבות או להפעיל את הכל בקלות דרך ההגדרות, כדי שתוכלו ללחוץ בשקט.
        </description>

        <news>
            v1.0.5 - [Bug Fix] Fixed additional bugs in the strings.po translation file.
            [Cleanup] Removed old and unused localization string entries from the translation file.
            [Bug Fix] Fixed an issue in the settings.xml configuration file.

            v1.0.4 - Translation bug fixes.

            v1.0.3 - Translation bug fixes.

            v1.0.2 - [Security Fix] Introduced a single, mandatory access point (get_provider_token) for reading
            any credential from POV, used by all six providers — Trakt, TorBox, AllDebrid, Real-Debrid, Premiumize,
            and EasyNews. Any token logging now automatically goes through masking (last 4 characters visible only),
            instead of relying on each call site to remember to mask it.
            [Bug Fix] Fixed "Can't find window keyboard" error: corrected the window name used to detect the
            on-screen keyboard from "keyboard" to the correct Kodi window name "virtualkeyboard", across all
            checks (boot sequence, player overlay, and the Guardian loop).

            [Feature] The "connect now?" prompt (previously only shown for Trakt/TorBox) now appears
            for all 6 supported providers — AllDebrid, Real-Debrid, Premiumize, and EasyNews are included too.
            [Bug Fix] Added missing localization strings for AllDebrid, Real-Debrid, Premiumize, and EasyNews
            status messages — they were referenced by the code but missing from strings.po, causing blank text
            during boot for those providers.

            v1.0.1 - Added support for service providers — Trakt, TorBox, AllDebrid, Real-Debrid, Premiumize and EasyNews.
            On first install, select which providers to enable — checked on every boot.
            If not connected, a prompt appears to connect directly without digging through POV settings.

            v1.0.0 - First stable release.
            Added startup and playback protection overlays,
            memory cleanup on fast exit, and 3 quick back-key force-stop mechanism.
        </news>

    </extension>

</addon>
</addons>
